President's Office Records, 1927-1981
University of Houston Libraries
- Subject Files (Box 1-50)
  - Cullen, Mrs. Lillie, 1956-1960 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Cullen, Naming University for, 1947-1957 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Cullen Plaza Dedication, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Cullen Plaza Dedication, 1973 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Cullen Portraits, 1960-1967 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Cullen Rifles, 1952-1957 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Cullens - Two Great Texans, The, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Czech - Letters re: Teaching, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Czech - Letters re: Teaching, 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Dadd, Sharon (Mrs. Bruce), 1972 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Danforth Foundation, 1957-1969 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Danforth Foundation, 1969-1973 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Danforth Foundation, 1975-1977 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Dean of Students, 1957-1961 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Dean of Students, 1962-1965 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Dean of Students, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Dean of Women, 1967-1971 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Dean's Discretionary Fund, 1963-1970 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Dean's Discretionary Accounts, 1971-1978 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Deans - Duties, 1951-1957 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Dean's Meetings, 1968-1970 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Dean's Meetings, 1975-1976 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Delphian Society, 1966-1974 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Democratic Society, 1968-1972 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Department Chairman's Conference, 1963-1971 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Development Contacts, 1973-1976 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Development Council, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Development, Miscellaneous, 1967-1971 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Development Office, 1956-1972 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Development Office, 1975-1978 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Diplomas, 1957-1975 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Directories - Miscellaneous, 1956-1972 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Discretionary Funds, 1975-1976 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Dormitories - General, 1956-1973 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Dormitories - Naming of, 1955-1956 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Dormitory Buildings, Construction of, 1950-1952 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Doctoral Programs, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Dow Chemical Company, 1963-1973 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Downtown College, University of Houston (Box 20, Folder 1-28)
    - Administration/Downtown School, 1955-1971 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Press Release announcing UH Acquisition of South Texas Junior College, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Acquisition of Assets, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Administrative Re-organization, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Administration/Degrees Proposed, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Administrative Files, 1974 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Administration/Available Funds and Long-range Space Needs Planning, 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Re-organization Proposal & Response to Southern Association Visiting Committee Report, 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - First Draft of Visiting Committee Report to the Southern Association, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Administration/Degrees Proposed, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Administration/Student Fees, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Administration/Budget, 1975 (Box 20, Folder 12-13)
    - Inspection Reports and Project Planning, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Administration/Tenure Policy, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Administration/Budget, 1976-1977 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Administration/Building and Traffic, 1977 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Administrative Files, 1978-1979 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Administrative Correspondence, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Report: Administration and Student Services Formula Study Committee, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Report: Response to the Evaluation Committee Visitation Report, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - National Registry of Historical Places, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Campus Security Committee, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Vacations and Absences, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Chancellor's Expenditures, Vouchers, 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Student Handbook, Drafts of Suggested Changes, 1979-1980 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Chancellor Search Committee, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Leestamper, Robert (Chancellor Search), 1980 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Drama, Department of, 1946-1949 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Drama, Department of, 1950-1959 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Drama, Department of, 1964-1973 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Dual Employment, 1963-1972 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - "E" Citation and Ceremony, 1966 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Ebaugh, Bessie, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Economic Opportunity, Office of, 1965-1972 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Economics Doctoral Program, 1958-1959 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Education, College of, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Education, College of, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Education, College of, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Education, College of, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 9-11)
  - Education, College of, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Education, College of, 1976-1979 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Education, National Council for Accreditation of Teacher Education, 1961-1963 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Education, National Council for Accreditation of Teacher Education, 1964-1968 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Education, National Council for Accreditation of Teacher Education, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Education, National Council for Accreditation of Teacher Education, 1970-1974 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Educational Directory, 1969-1978 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Elgin-Scott Property, 1972 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Ellington Air Force Base, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Elliot, Bill County Judge, 1970-1973 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Emeriti - Professors, 1959-1973 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Emeriti - Professors, 1975-1978 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Emerson and Company, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Energy Foundation of Texas, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Energy Foundation of Texas, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 26-27)
  - Energy Foundation of Texas, 1977-1979 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Energy Institute, 1973 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Energy Institute, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Energy Institute, 1974-1975 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Energy Institute, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Energy Institute, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Energy Institute, undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Engineering Building Dedication, 1967-1968 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Engineering, College of, 1977-1979 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Engineering, College of, undated (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Engineering, College of, 1973-1974 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Engineering, College of, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Engineering, College of, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Engineering, College of, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Engineering, College of, 1974-1979 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Cullen College of Engineering Minority Recruiting, 1972-1974 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Engineering Study, 1955 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Engineer's Council for Professional Development, 1964-1967 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - English Department, 1971-1974 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - English-Doctor of Philosophy, 1958-1967 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Enrollment, 1974 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Enrollment, 1975 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Enrollment 1975-1977, 1975-1978 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity Council, 1974-1977 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Ex-Students' Association, 1954-1956 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - "Extended Neighborhood" Study Hendrick Douglass Friedman Group, 1978 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Extension Services, 1935-1964 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Exxon Company, USA, 1939-1967 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Exxon Company, USA, 1968-1969 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Exxon Company, USA, 1972-1976 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Exxon Foundation Grants, 1975-1977 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Ezekiel W. Cullen Building, 1945-1946 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Ezekiel W. Cullen Building, 1947 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Ezekiel W. Cullen Building, 1948 (Box 23, Folder 5-7)
  - Ezekiel W. Cullen Building, 1949 (Box 23, Folder 8-9)
  - Ezekiel W. Cullen Building, 1950-1957 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Ezekiel W. Cullen Building, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Ezekiel W. Cullen Building, undated (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Ezekiel W. Cullen Building - Cornerstone Laying, 1948-1955 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Ezekiel W. Cullen Building - Dedication, 1950-1951 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Ezekiel W. Cullen Building - Equipment, 1950 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Ezekiel W. Cullen Building - Equipment, 1950-1951 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Facilities Planning and Construction, 1976-1977 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Faculty and Professional Women's Association, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Faculty and Staff Manuals, 1968-1975 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Faculty and Staff Manual, 1971-1977 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Faculty - Benefits, 1953-1965 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Faculty Central Campus, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Faculty Clear Lake City, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Faculty Club, 1951-1974 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Faculty Dance Club, 1965-1971 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Faculty Dance Club, 1971-1975 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Faculty Development Leave, 1976-1977 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Faculty Development Programs, 1976-1977 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Faculty Downtown, 1980 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Faculty Federation, 1973-1976 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Faculty General Meeting, 1968-1974 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Faculty General Meeting, 1971-1974 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Faculty General Meeting, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 33-34)
  - Faculty General Meeting, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Faculty Handbook, 1959-1966 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Faculty Interview Fund, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Luncheon, 1968-1973 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Faculty New Members, leave, retired, 1973-1977 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Faculty New Positions Requested, 1968-1970 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Policies, 1955-1965 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Promotions, 1969-1970 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Promotions, 1971-1972 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Promotions, 1972-1976 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Faculty-Promotion and Tenure, 1976-1977 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Promotion and Tenure, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Promotion and Tenure, 1979 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Research Support Program, 1969-1970 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Retirement and Non-renewal, 1971-1978 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Salaries, 1969-1973 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Salaries, 1975-1977 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Faculty Senate, 1969-1970 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Faculty Senate, 1972-1976 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Faculty Senate, 1975-1976 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Faculty Senate, 1974-1977 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Faculty Senate General Correspondence, 1970-1973 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Faculty Senate General Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Faculty Senate General Correspondence, 1972 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Faculty Senate General Correspondence, 1973 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Faculty Senate General Correspondence, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Faculty - Sex Discrimination, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Faculty - Unionization, 1972-1974 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Faculty Victoria Campus, 1980 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Faculty Workload Report, 1978-1980 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Fall Semester Twelfth Class Day Enrollment, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Farfel Lectures, 1969-1974 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Farfel Lectures, 1974 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - Farish Hall Dedication, April 2, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Farish, Mrs. Stephen P., 1973-1975 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Fazekas, Gabriel-Mechanical Engineer, 1976-1978 (Box 24, Folder 34)
  - Federal Bureau of Investigation, 1967-1970 (Box 24, Folder 35)
  - Feld, M. M., Correspondence with, 1956-1960 (Box 24, Folder 36)
  - Field House, Committee for the Univ. of Houston 1969-1970 (Box 24, Folder 37)
  - Field House - Proposed, 1957-1962 (Box 24, Folder 38)
  - Fiftieth Anniversary Convocation, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 39)
  - Financial Report - UH, 1972-1973 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Financial Statements [Reports?], 1977 (Box 25, Folder 2-3)
  - Financial Reports, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 4-5)
  - Financial Reports, 1979 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Fine Arts Center, 1964-1975 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Finn, Alfred C. - Architect, 1944-1948 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Finn, Alfred C. - Architect, 1949-1964 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - First City National Bank, 1977-1980 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Five Year Planning Data (1969-1974), 1971 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Flag-General Policies regarding display of U.S., 1961-1970 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Flag Pole, 1939-1940 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Flag-U.H.-Policies regarding lowering of, undated (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Fleetwood Pre-Columbian Collection, 1964-1975 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Fleming Building - Dedication of, 1965 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Fleming, Mrs. Claire B., 1963-1965 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Food Services, 1962-1967 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Ford, President Gerald, 1974-1977 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Ford Foundation, 1969-1974 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Ford Foundation, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Foreign Language, Division of, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Foreign Language, Division of, 1974-1979 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Forum, 1969-1974 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Forum, 1974-1977 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Foundation Creole, 1966 (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Foundation, UH (Box 25, Folder 27-57)
    - Financial Statement, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - General, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Meeting, November 22, 1977 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - U.H. 50 Meeting, February 17, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Special Meeting, March 29, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Meeting, June 12, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Meeting, November 20, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Portfolio Analysis, January 1978 (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - Portfolio Analysis, February 1978 (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - Portfolio Analysis, March 1978 (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - Portfolio Analysis, April 1978 (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - Portfolio Analysis, May 1978 (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - Portfolio Analysis, June 1978 (Box 25, Folder 39)
    - Portfolio Analysis, July 1978 (Box 25, Folder 40)
    - Portfolio Analysis, August 1978 (Box 25, Folder 41)
    - Portfolio Analysis, September 1978 (Box 25, Folder 42)
    - Portfolio Analysis, October 1978 (Box 25, Folder 43)
    - Portfolio Analysis, November 1978 (Box 25, Folder 44)
    - Portfolio Analysis, December 1978 (Box 25, Folder 45)
    - Portfolio Analysis, January 1979 (Box 25, Folder 46)
    - Portfolio Analysis, February 1979 (Box 25, Folder 47)
    - Portfolio Analysis, March 1979 (Box 25, Folder 48)
    - Portfolio Analysis, April 1979 (Box 25, Folder 49)
    - Portfolio Analysis, May 1979 (Box 25, Folder 50)
    - Portfolio Analysis, June 1979 (Box 25, Folder 51)
    - Portfolio Analysis, July 1979 (Box 25, Folder 52)
    - Portfolio Analysis, August 1979 (Box 25, Folder 53)
    - Portfolio Analysis, September 1979 (Box 25, Folder 54)
    - Portfolio Analysis, October 1979 (Box 25, Folder 55)
    - Portfolio Analysis, November 1979 (Box 25, Folder 56)
    - Portfolio Analysis, December 1979 (Box 25, Folder 57)
  - Founders Day Program, 1936-1952 (Box 25, Folder 58)
  - Frederica Gross Dudley Hall, 1971-1973 (Box 25, Folder 59)
  - Frontier Fiesta - Critique and Comments, 1957 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Frontier Fiesta - History, Clippings, and Handbook, 1957-1961 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Fruit Basket, 1971-1974 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Fulbright Advisor, 1964-1977 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Fulbright Foundation, 1958-1960 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Fultz, Larry - Director of Security, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Furniture - Office of the President, 1966-1972 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Furniture - Office of the President, 1972-1975 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Galveston County Junior College, 1965 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - G.E. College Bowl, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence, 1976-1979 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - General Electric Company, 1961-1972 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Geology - Advisory Committee, 1955-1969 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Geology, Department of, 1968-1974 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Geology, Department of, undated (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Geology Foundation, 1969-1975 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Gonzales, Richard J., 1965-1973 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Gordon Foundation, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Governor and Lt. Governor - State of Texas, 1957-1965 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Governor and Lt. Governor - State of Texas, 1966-1970 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Governor and Lt. Governor - State of Texas, 1971-1972 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Governor and Lt. Governor - State of Texas, 1973-1974 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Governor, State of Texas, 1974-1977 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Governor's Committee on Education beyond the High School, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Governor's Committee on Public School Education, 1968-1973 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Graduate Council, 1973-1974 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Graduate Council, 1976-1977 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Graduate Research Center, 1967 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Graham, Billy, 1965-1967 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Grand Jury Investigation, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Gulf Oil Corporation, 1962-1978 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - Gulf University Research Corporation, 1968-1970 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Hagen, Dr. Fred, 1965-1968 (Box 26, Folder 33)
  - Half Century Celebration, 1976-1978 (Box 26, Folder 34)
  - Harman, Cynthia A. Senior Secretary, 1977-1978 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Harpoon, The, 1969 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Harvard Institute for College and University Administrators - Correspondence, 1956-1962 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Harvard Institute for College and University Administrators - Publications, 1957-1964 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Harvard University, 1964-1980 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Harvest, The, 1940-1973 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Harvest, The, 1973-1975 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Hawn Foundation, 1962-1963 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Hazelwood Act, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Hazelwood Act (Attorney's Opinion), 1961-1962 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Health and Physical Education, 1962-1977 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Health, Education and Welfare, 1971-1972 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Health, Education and Welfare, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Health, Education and Welfare, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 14-15)
  - Health, Education and Welfare, 1974 (Box 27, Folder 16-17)
  - Health, Education and Welfare, 1975 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Health, Education and Welfare, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Health, Education and Welfare-U.S. Department, 1976-1977 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Health Services, 1964-1971 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Health Services, 1972-1973 (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Health Services, 1974-1977 (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - High Schools, 1960-1970 (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - High Schools-College Conference (Annual), 1958-1967 (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Hilton, Conrad N., 1969 (Box 27, Folder 26)
  - Hispanic Civilization Program in Spain Media Coverage, 1975-1976 (Box 27, Folder 27)
  - History, Department of, 1957-1965 (Box 27, Folder 28)
  - History, Department of, 1966-1974 (Box 27, Folder 29)
  - Hobby, Oveta Culp, 1952-1960 (Box 27, Folder 30)
  - Hobby, Oveta Culp, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 31)
  - Hoff, Joan E., 1966 (Box 27, Folder 32)
  - Hoffman-Congratulations, 1962-1977 (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Hofheinz, Judge Roy, 1969-1974 (Box 27, Folder 34)
  - Hofheinz Pavilion, Use of, 1970-1974 (Box 27, Folder 35)
  - Hofheinz Pavilion, Use of, 1974-1977 (Box 27, Folder 36)
  - Hogg Foundation, 1941-1964 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Hogg Foundation, 1970 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Home Economics, Department of, 1956-1973 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Home Economics Model Home, 1955-1956 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Honorariums-University Employees, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Honorary Degrees-Policy, 1957-1978 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Honors Day, 1971-1972 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Honors Day, 1973 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Honors Day, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Honors Day, April 14, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Honors Day, April 30, 1976 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Honors Graduates, 1955-1962 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Honors Programs, 1968-1972 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Honors Programs Council, 1963-1971 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Horlock Foundation, 1968 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Hotel, Restaurant Management, School of, 1969-1973 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Management, College of, 1973-1977 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Hotel and Restaurant Management, College of, 1978-1979 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - House Bill 291, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - House Bill 6143, 1963-1964 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Housing, 1962-1969 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Housing, 1970-1974 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Houston Baptist College, 1960-1974 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Houston Baptist College, 1975 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Houston Chronicle, 1964-1977 (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Houston, City of (Council and Mayor), 1970-1974 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Houston Community College System, 1971-1977 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Houston Endowment, Inc., 1963-1972 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Houston Independent School District - Miscellaneous, 1935-1950 (Box 28, Folder 29)
  - Houston Independent School District - Miscellaneous, 1951-1969 (Box 28, Folder 30)
  - Houston Independent School District - Special Laws, 1923 (Box 28, Folder 31)
  - Houston Independent School District, 1970-1972 (Box 28, Folder 32)
  - Houston Intercontinental Airport, 1969 (Box 28, Folder 33)
  - Houston International Trade and Travel Inc., 1961 (Box 28, Folder 34)
  - Houston Law Review, 1962-1974 (Box 28, Folder 35)
  - Houston Law Review, 1974 (Box 28, Folder 36)
  - Houston Lighting and Power, Co., 1971-1972 (Box 28, Folder 37)
  - Houston Metropolitan Archives, 1974-1977 (Box 28, Folder 38)
  - Houston Rockets, 1971-1972 (Box 28, Folder 39)
  - Houston Southwest Institute for Urban Studies, 1968-1969 (Box 28, Folder 40)
  - Human Resources Institute, 1967 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Humanities, Commission on the, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Humble Oil Foundation, 1964-1972 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Hyer, Dr. June, 1970-1972 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - IBM, 1965-1976 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Inauguration, President UH, 1962 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Inauguration - Rice University, 1971 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Inauguration - Stevens, John Christopher, 1969-1970 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Information, Office of, 1969-1974 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Information, Office of, Central Campus, 1974-1977 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Institute of Religion, 1968-1971 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Institute for Science and Technology Management, 1966-1967 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Institute for Urban Studies, 1973-1974 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Institute for Urban Studies, 1968-1977 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Institutional Studies, Office of, 1967-1970 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Institutional Studies, Office of, 1971-1973 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Integration, 1955-1956 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Integration, 1957-1961 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Integration, 1962-1969 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Integration - Graduate, 1956 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Integration - Graduate, 1958-1962 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Integration - Undergraduate, 1956 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Integration - Undergraduate, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Integration - Undergraduate, 1958-1962 (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - International Affairs Council, 1968-1970 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - International Affairs, Office of, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - International Affairs, Office of, 1973-1974 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - International Center for Education, 1975-1979 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - International Student Office, 1971-1972 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - International Student Office, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - International Student Office, 1974 (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - International Student Office, 1974-1978 (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - Interscholastic League, 1953-1974 (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - Jeppeson Stadium Appraisal, 1963 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Jeppeson Stadium Appraisal, 1967-1971 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Jeppeson Stadium, 1970-1971 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Jeppeson Stadium, 1971-1972 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Johnson, Dr. Alan W., 1964-1965 (Box 30, Folder 5)